Name 1: Jared Evans
Student Number 1: n8288305
Name 2: Daniel Knoblanche
Student Number 2: n7138288

Statement of Contribution 1:
Daniel did literally all of the testing. Literally all of it. My focus was on the programming part, because my testing marks for Assignment 1 were so-so. Daniel proof read alot to find alot of mistakes in the code; as well as helped with all the commenting - he helped catch incorrect exceptions, incorrect states that I would not have found on my own so easily.
Statement of Contribution 2:
Ditto what he said.
We both agree with what is written.

Bugs / Incomplete Features
Everything closes when you close any chart / window. (bonus feature!)
Our defaults log matched yours. Our longStay log and smallCars log matched yours to begin with, but stopped matching halfway through. The counts were different at the end (so we created more or less vehicles then you: which doesn't make sense, that's the easy part), we have NO idea if we're right or if you're right.
ChartPanel.java is a wreck. It works. It looks bad.
We will provide you with a run.bat
Our main method is in SimulationRunner.java
Libraries used: junit/hamcrest for testing and jfreechart/jcommon for charts.
https://github.com/N7138288/Assignment-2/commits?page=1
This is the closest thing to a git log that we both know.
Have a nice day. : )
